A Guide to the Papers of Rear Admiral Walter C. Ansel, 1924-1974
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence with Publishers, Books, Stores, and Libraries
    - An das Institut fur Zeitgeschichte, 1953-1954 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Landesbibliothek, 1953 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Alfred Metzer Verlag, 1960 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Mohrbooks Literary Agency, 1960-1961 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Pforzheimer Zeitung, 1953 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Verlag Hans-Henning Podzun, 1953 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 53)
    - An den Sueddeutschen Rundfunk, 1953 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Verlag Ullstein/Bilderdienst, 1953 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Wehr and Wissen Verlagsgesellschaft, 1972 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - Baxter, Dr. James P., 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bennett, John, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Bittrich, Friedrich Otto, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Brall, Emil, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Bredt, Alexander, 1954 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Brooks, B.T., 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Dienban, Richard, 1970 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Eurue, Dr., 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Flemming, Peter, 1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Gardner, Dr. C.H., 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Gatzke, Hans (no date) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hartwig, Ingeborg, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hathaway, Mike, 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Hinsley, F.H., 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Kinderlen, Heinz, 1957 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Klee, Dr. Karl, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Koch, Dr. Justus, 1953-1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Kochler, Dr. Wolfgang, 1953-1954 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Krausnick, Dr., 1956 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Melas, William, 1973 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Melland, Brian, 1953-1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Milch, Erhard, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Pfeiffer, Oswin Cornelius, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Pfeider, Dr. Karl George, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Pfeider, Dr. Otto, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Plesman, Dr. Albert, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Plocher, Herman, 1954-1956 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Possony, Dr., 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Rommel, Lucy, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Roginski, Dr. Herbert, 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Rohwer, Dr. Klaus-Jurgen, 1953-1957 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Saunders, James M., 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Schack, Klaus-Dieter, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Schafer-Schwartzkopff, Urula, 1953-1974 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Seidenschwann, Alfres, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Taham, Dr. George K., 1952-1954 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Uhlig, Dr. Heinrich, 1953-1956 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 37)
    - White, John C., 1969 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Wilcox, Adam, 1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Worden, W.L., 1955-1957 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Wormann, Dr. Ernst, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Personal Correspondence
    - Ansel Family, 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Asprey, Robert B., 1957-1958 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Bauer, Jack, 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Bellande, Henry, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Binder, L.O., 1954 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Chinese Navy Representatives, 1952-1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Demarest, Clayton, 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Eisenhower, President Dwight D., 1956 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Genz, Walter, 1955, 1962 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Gilmore, Russ, 1956 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Goverment Printing Office, 1957 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Heitinan, R., 1953-1964 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Ives, Burl, 1957 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Keegan, William A., 1957 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Kerr, George, 1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Manchester, Alan K., 1970 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Mas. R., 1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 58)
    - McCabe, H.V., 1937 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Metzel, Truman, 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Moore, Houston, 1960 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Pantaleo, T.T., 1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Pinto, Paulo A.S., 1958 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Riggs National Bank, 1957 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 64)
    - J. Salmon Limited, 1953-1960 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Ben Sayers, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Scrivner, Parker, and Clarke, 1972 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Shields, Bill, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Stephens, William P., 1956 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Tranter, P., 1972 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 71)
    - U.S. Post Office, 1955 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 72)
    - U.S. Veterans Administration, 1953 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Wagner, W.L., 1958 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Unidentified Correspondence (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Form Letters (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 76)
- Photographs of Individuals, Amphibious Equipment, Fortifications, and Other Military Related Pictures Used by Ansel in his Research
  - Individuals
    - Ansel, Rear Admiral Walter C. (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Bartels, Kapitan zur See Heinrich (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Blumentritt, General der Infantrie Gunther (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Brodruck, Major (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Bukholz, General Ulich (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Feiraband, General with family and Admiral Ansel (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 6)
    - von Gyldenfedt, Oberst Leutnant (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Halder, General Oberst Fritz (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Heusinger, General Leutnant Adolf (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Hitler, Adolf with Marshal Antonesu (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Hitler, Adolf and Hermann Goering at the signing of the Armistist (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Hitler, Adolf and Hermann Goering in the Reich Chancellery, 1939/1940 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Hitler's Headquarters at Wolfsschlucht, Belgium (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Hitler and his High Command (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Hitler, Adolf and Marshal Mannerheim (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Hitler, Adolf and Bunito Mussolini (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Hitler, Adolf and his naval aid von Puttkamer (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Hitler, Adolf and Grossadmiral Dr. Erich Raeder (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Hitler, Adolf and Generalfeldmarshal von Rundstedt (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Hitler, Adolf at the Russian Campaign Conference (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Hitler, Adolf, General Schmudt, and Kapitan zur See von Puttkamer (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Hitler and his Staff (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Hitler at Warsaw, Poland (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 23)
    - List, Generalfeldmarshal (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Junge, Kapitan zur See Wolf (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Kesselring, Generalfeldmarshal Albert and General Erwin Rommel (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Lehmann, Kapitan zur See (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Loch, General leutnant Herbert and Family (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Reinike, Kapitan zur See and Admiral Ansel (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Ringel, General der Gebrias Julius (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Ringel, General der Gebrias Julius and General Kurt Student (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 31)
    - von Runstedt, Generalfeldmarshal (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Schniewind, Generaladmiral Otto (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Strauss, General Oberst (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Student, General Kurt (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Wagner, Konteradmiral Gehard and wife (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Military Related
    - Map of Europe and North Africa (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Report by General der Falls H. Ramke (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 38)
    - U.S. Sixth Fleet at Gibraltar (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 1)
    - American; British, and French ships at Malta (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 2)
    - German Landing sites for Operation Sea Lion (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Martello Towers Hythe Dyme Church, England (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Martello Towers Hythe Dyme Church, England (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Martello Towers Hythe Dyme Church, England (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Hythe Beach, England (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Grand Redoubt Byrne Church, England (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Hythe from the ridge, England (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Folkstone, England (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Dover Cliffs and the Coast Line, England (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Beachy Head Cliff, France (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Dungeness Circular Grand Redoubt, France (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Dieppe Water Port, France (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Dunkirk Harbor, France (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Boulogne Waterfront, France (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cap Gric Nex gun in placement (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Cap Blanc Neax gun in placement (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Ticket from Calais to Dover, French (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Training Beach for German troops getting ready for Operation Sea Lion. Ostend, France (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Bastogone, France, 17 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Landing craft that was to be used in Operation Sea Lion (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Landing craft that was to be used in Operation Sea Lion (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Landing craft that was to be used in Operation Sea Lion (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Landing craft that was to be used in Operation Sea Lion (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Landing craft that was to be used in Operation Sea Lion (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Landing Maneuvers at Laharve and Seine (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Landing Maneuvers at Laharve and Seine (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Landing Maneuvers at Laharve, September-October 1940 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Landing Maneuvers at Laharve, France (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Types of Transports used in Operation Sea Lion (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Breskins, Holland (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 32)
    - British wartime photos of Greece (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 33)
    - British wartime photos of Greece (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 34)
    - British wartime photos of Greece (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 35)
    - British wartime photos of Greece (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Landscape of Greece (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Landscape of Crete (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 46)
    - German Bomber (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 1)
    - German soldiers under fire (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 2)
    - German troops in brush (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Downed German planes (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 4)
    - German paratroopers (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 5)
    - German paratroopers with an anti-tank gun (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 6)
    - German paratroopers (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Paratroopers in the brush (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Resting Paratroopers on a hillside (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Wounded soldiers (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Greek fishing boats used in the amphibious landing on Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Landing of Paratroops (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Landing of Paratroops (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Battle series of shots on Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Map of Crete (negative) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Map of Central Europe and the Mediterranean (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Bohme, General and his staff car in Greece (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Canal of Corinth, Greece, 1941 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 18)
    - German convoys moving through Greece (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Motorcycle troops and motorcycle (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Metanas line of anti-tank obstacles, Greece, 1941 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 21)
    - German Luftwaffe officers at lunch table, Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Negatives of the German Luftwaffe 11 Flieger Korps in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Printed material of German combat pictures (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Crete Landscape (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Monadrendri signal hill range (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Coastal road from Axis Marina toward Platanias (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Signal Hill (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 51)
    - German paratroopers in the field (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 52)
    - German paratrooper march in a parade in Athens, Greece (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 53)
    - German troops crossing to Crete (no photo) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Mountain infantry troops in Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Landing of troops by sea, Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Canal of Corinth (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 57)
    - German Ju 87's over Greece (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 58)
    - German Map of Greece and Crete (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 59)
    - German invasion photo on metal plate (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 60)
    - German invasion photo on metal plate (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 61)
    - German invasion photo on metal plate (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 62)
- Documents of the German Military during World War II
  - German Armed Forces High Comand (O.K.W. - Wehrmacht)
    - O.K.W. report on struggle of forces against England, 29 Nov. 1939 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 1)
    - O.K.W. message to the Supreme Commander of the Army, 18 Jan. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 2)
    - O.K.W. message to the Supreme Commander of the Navy, 29 Mar. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 3)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 26 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 4)
    - O.K.W. report on war against England, 2 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 5)
    - O.K.W. message to the Supreme Commander of the Army, 15 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 6)
    - O.K.W. report on Operation Sea Lion, 1 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 7)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 5 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 8)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 7 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 9)
    - O.K.W. report on Operation Sea Lion, 16 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 10)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 27 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 11)
    - O.K.W. memo on plans for Operation Sea Lion, 7 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 12)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 9 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 13)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 2 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 14)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 10 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 15)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 13 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 16)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 22 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 17)
    - O.K.W. report on War against Western Powers, 30 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 18)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 10 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 19)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 10. Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 20)
    - O.K.W. message to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, Operations Branch, 21 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 21)
    - O.K.W. message to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, Operations Branch, 1 Feb. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 22)
    - O.K.W. message to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, Operations Branch, 24 Feb. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 23)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 30 Jun. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 24)
    - O.K.W. message to all military branches, 15 Aug. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Supreme Command to the German Air Force (O.K.L. - Luffwaffe)
    - O.K.L. message to the Supreme Commander of the Army, 30 Dec. 1939 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 26)
    - O.K.L. message to the Supreme Commander of the Navy, 14 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 27)
    - O.K.L. message to the Supreme Commander of the Navy, 8 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 28)
    - O.K.L. message to all military branches, 2 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Airfleet 2 report on Operation Sea Lion, 17 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Airfleet 2 report on Operation Sea Lion, 29 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Airfleet 2 message to Supreme Commander Naval Group West, 7 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Airfleet 2 message to all military branches, 12 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Airfleet 2 report on Operation Sea Lion, 18 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Ninth Bomber Division to Airfleet 2, 22 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Supreme Command ot the German Army (O.K.H. - Heeres)
    - O.K.H. report to the Chief of the Naval War Staff, 13 Dec. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 36)
    - O.K.H. message to the Supreme Commander of the Navy, 21 May 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 37)
    - O.K.H. message to the Supreme Commander of the Navy, 12 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 38)
    - O.K.H. message to the Supreme Commander of the Navy, 15 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 39)
    - O.K.H. memo to other military branches, 24 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 40)
    - O.K.H. memo to O.K.W., 26 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 41)
    - O.K.H. memo to Army Operations Department, 30 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 42)
    - O.K.H. memo to Supreme Commander of Navy, 31 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 43)
    - O.K.H. memo to O.K.W., O.K.M., and their Chiefs of Staffs, 10 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 44)
    - O.K.H. memo to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 18 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 45)
    - O.K.H. report on "Kusten Kampf," 21 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 46)
    - O.K.H. memo to all military branches, 31 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 47)
    - O.K.H. reports on "Instructions of preparations for Sea Lion to other military branches," 30 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 48)
    - O.K.H. memo to other military branches, 4 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 49)
    - O.K.H. memo to O.K.H. and O.K.M., 12 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 50)
    - O.K.H. memo to O.K.W., 10 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 51)
    - O.K.H. memo to other military branches, 13 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 52)
    - O.K.H. memo to Chief of Staff to the Naval War Staff, 6 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 53)
    - O.K.H. memo to the O.K.M., 17 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 54)
    - O.K.H. memo to Chief of Staff to the Naval War Staff, 13 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 55)
    - O.K.H. memo to Chief of Staff of the Army General Staff, 24 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 56)
    - O.K.H. memo to Chief of Staff to the Naval War Staff, 22 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 57)
    - O.K.H. memo to O.K.M., 28 Jan. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 58)
    - O.K.H. memo to O.K.W, 26 Aug. 1941 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Chief of Staff of the Army General Staff to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 14 Jul. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Army Group A to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 10 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Army Group A report on Operation Sea Lion's Preparations, 14 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Army Group A memo to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 30 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Army Group A memo to the Chief of Staff of the Naval War Staff, 4 Nov. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Army Group Nine memo to the Chief of Staff of the Army General Staff, 9 Oct. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Army Command of the Troops in the Netherlands report on Operation Herbstreise, 25 Aug. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Seventeenth Infantry Division report on preparations for Sea Lion, 12 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Seventeenth Infantry Division report on Plan for England, 14 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 68)
    - O.K.H. report on Air War in the West, 11 Sept. 1940 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 69)
    - O.K.H. charts on Operation Sea Lion (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Supreme commander in Chief of the German Navy (Ob.d.M)
    - Ob.d.M. report on North Sea Operations, 1 Oct. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Ob.d.M. meeting minutes with the Fuehrer, 16 Oct. 1939 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 2)